Main gate is clear. No movement of civilians or vehicles.
Clear.
Entry complete.
Copy.
Moving to the basement in 30 seconds.
Five-minute-interval check-in.
Roger.
Marco, M, secure the basement server on level one.
The rest you, follow me to the mall.
Yes, chief!
Pasin, what happened to my uncle and Minhye?
Pasin
Don't do this.
Stay still.
It's all over.
I got Jian now.
Let Atti go.
Pasin, it's me.
Hold for a second.
-  Dad. - Atti?
Are you all right?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine.
I'm okay. Really okay.
Atti? Everything is going to be okay now, Atti!
Atti.
You saved my son.
- Thank you, Jinman. -  No, don't thank me.
Starting from now on, I'm your son's kidnapper.
Listen carefully.
Stop being Babylon's little puppet.
Protect your son by protecting Jian.
Make sure that Jian doesn't die!
Remember, Pasin, your son's life is on the line.
What about my uncle?
Jinman is all right, Jian.
I am sorry about everything.
I'll explain all of it later.
We have to leave.
Hurry, Jian.
Okay, keep going.
-  Get her alive! -  Brother!
:cue
Go!
The gun at the end.
Hold tight.
Be careful.
Go, little slug.
Master.
Master!
That door
It can't be opened from here.
Listen up, Jeong Jian.
There could be a situation where you lose an arm.
What happens then? Don't try to recover the arm you lost.
You should protect the one you still have.
We have to go.
- Where is Jeong Jian? -  In there.
Pull the handle on the last rifle.
- I'm going after her. - Yes, chief!
:cue
Shit.
We're almost there. You have to get up, okay?
We're almost there.
Brother.
You you go first.
- Better hurry up, Jian. - That's not allowed.
Stand up. Give me your arm.
I need just a minute to rest.
We're almost there.
Brother, get up.
We're going together.
What?
Hey, stupid shit. This isn't funny.
Open the door. Open it!
Brother, open the door!
-  Jeong Jian. -  Open the door!
- Thank you for everything. Go live. -  Open the door!
Brother, please open the door! Open it!
- Hyung -  Brother, open the door!
See you in a few minutes.
Stop it.
Don't do it.
Son of a bitch!
Breaching.
Move into the underground passage.
Right now!
Oh, right in front of it, there's a small room,
Like the old shopping mall.
From there, you can just
- burn the whole shopping mall down. -  Why?
Why?
Your escaping through means that's an emergency situation :cue
And you can't leave any traces behind.
Retreat!
Wow, you killed everyone.
Jian, do you get it now?
The kind of hell you'll have to live with.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2 :cue
EPISODE 07 THE ENEMY OF MY ENEMY
So, what do I get out of this?
If you manage to persuade the Code Reds for us,
We'll provide free weapons.
For every operation completed, there's a separate profit-sharing rate.
Guaranteed.
That's very generous.
But as you've probably heard,
I've been retired from this business for a long time.
What exactly do you get out of being so generous to a washed-up guy like me? Hm?
It seems all the Code Reds take orders from you.
That's why we're here.
When you make a move, they all follow.
That entire network also happens to include the client list that we want.
I get that. But that's fallen apart by now.
Just us small fries left.
Well, that happens to be what big corporations fear.
Start-ups and the relentless small fries.
For instance, Jeong Jinman's murthehelp. It's a good business model.
Speaking of Jinman
If you're able to capture Jeong Jinman or Jeong Jian,
Babylon will kindly offer you this token of goodwill.
:cue
From now on, all the Code Greens are under protection.
So, um
Are you Kusanagi or Jin? I'm confused.
Are you Korean or Japanese?
You're taking the money back?
Fine. Okay.
I'm Korean. I've just been working in Japan for so long--
So you're saying you're a Korean woman using a Japanese surname?
Ms. Yoon Sujin?
One's nationality doesn't really matter, does it?
- We work on a global scale. -  Of course, it does.
It's not as simple as you think.
I'm the 37th generation of the Ahns of Sunheung
And the eldest grandson.
My direct ancestors include Ahn Junggeun and Ahn Changho.
What do you mean? For real?
Ah. Sorry.
I'd never take a Japanese name.
My ancestors died protecting our country from all those bastards.
We should all be working together.
Business is business.
It shouldn't matter whether we're Korean or Japanese.
It's not like you're here fighting for Korean independence.
Yeah, who am I? I'm not some guy trying to save my country.
The truth is
I don't like you.
You're a suit who looks like you've never gotten blood on your hands.
You believe that your money can buy you anything and keep your hands clean.
Yeah? You're disgusting.
You sit behind a desk while your subordinates do everything.
Jeez.
The Chosenjins have such a narrow view. The view
What's that?
Hey, you listen to me.
If you want to keep eating that meat you like so much,
You should be careful about what you say.
I could obliterate
This whole place right now.
Hm.
It's okay.
On something so trivial.
This meat's texture is worth the price.
Ahn Seongbeom, I understand your position.
It's always the cowards who show their teeth first.
Babylon doesn't put people behind a desk
Unless they've gotten blood on their hands. :cue
Spread out and find them.
Light in the face of death
Q! Q!
Are you okay?
This way.
Give me your gun.
There she is.
"JW."
BABYLON JW
JW UNION
YOUR FINAL JOURNEY. WE WILL ACCOMPANY YOU PEACEFULLY AND SAFELY
K, I have important information.
Yes, understood. The intelligence team will look into it.
I'll contact you with an update.
She decided to act on her own without reporting to me first.
- Should I tell her to return to the base? - No, it's all right.
Q can be preoccupied with catching Jeong Jian on her own.
We'll focus on capturing Jeong Jinman. :cue
We're gonna check out the other server on basement level one.
I wouldn't have worn this if I knew it'd be so filthy down here.
- Hey! - Me? Yes?
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
- Q survived all of this? -  Yeah.
That bitch has nine lives.
Hey, President Choi. What happened?
What?
Oh, noona, you're awake.
It's been a while.
Don't you have school?
We're on break.
Where are we?
Gonna answer it?
Should I?
Hello.
Jeong Jian.
Uncle.
So even after all that "sea of fire" bullshit,
You're telling me we still need Jeong Jinman and Jeong Jian?
Yes.
It's their biometric information that opens the location data
From murthehelp's codes.
You.
Why are you bouncing around, listening to music
As if you're being paid to half-ass your work?
Do you think you're here for college credit?
You seem to be treating this like some kind of part-time job or something.
If you children don't extract the data immediately,
You'll all disappear, never to be found again.
I'll put you all in a meat grinder. Understood?
- Is that clear? -  Yes.
Good.
Uh Sorry.
-  Hm? - I think I think
We might need better equipment.
Get whatever you need. :cue
So Minhye, she's as tough as they say.
She crawled out of the water on her own, even after she was shot.
She's lucky.
The bullet didn't hit any vital areas.
I can't believe Pasin would do that to her.
You can think of this place as Code Red's headquarters.
Doesn't look like much, but a tank couldn't get through this door.
It's made with a special alloy.
Most of these guns were purchased from your uncle.
When jobs come through murthehelp, Code Reds would come to this place.
It's more secure this way.
Collecting their weapons here prevents them from killing on impulse.
Jeong Jinman came up with that.
Hard to believe, but I used to manage all of this.
And thanks to someone, I guess I'm back.
My uncle mentioned this.
Hey. Are you sure?
Even if I'm not
I can't just sit and do nothing.
Jian.
It's good to go.
We've seized and taken over murthehelp's underground base.
Most of their operatives have been eliminated,
And we possess their data.
It's currently being analyzed.
Is there any risk this could become a problem?
Hm
Absolutely not.
They are going to hook our server into their supercomputer
To try to siphon data from murthehelp.
This is a functioning server, but in an emergency,
It's also an electric bomb.
If an unauthorized user tries to access it,
It'll overheat, disabling power completely within a one-kilometer radius.
They'll reboot it, but it'll take time.
It looks like we'll have about five minutes
On the server's emergency battery. :cue
But if the main base loses all power, wouldn't it be impossible to hack?
Maybe if you're trying to hack remotely.
Brother predicted this exact situation.
So we had the mole plant satellite comms inside.
We can extract their data at the same time.
Very good work, Branch Chief Kusanagi.
As promised, I'm allowing you to take managerial control of murthehelp.
I trust that you will be able to grow it into Babylon's business partner.
Yes. Thank you so much.
The time is right.
Make sure to rename murthehelp to something more fitting.
Of course, I'll take care of it.
One more thing.
How has Jeong Jinman been dealt with?
Prepare for brother's parting gift, you Babylon shitheads.
Jeong Jinman is
It worked.
Tell them to get the backup power online.
While they're all losing their minds trying to restore power,
All we have to do is connect our server that we swapped with their server.
- And that's it. -  I get it.
That's why there's a mole in Babylon, right?
Connection to mole complete.
It's my time to shine.
- How long? - One minute.
Reset the main breaker?
Hey, what's going on?
The backup power is up and running.
What's wrong with the server?
I almost had a heart attack, man.
What? Something's wrong.
What?
Open your damn mouth. What is it?
The inside of the server is, um, completely empty.
And now it's time to take a look.
What has Babylon been up to for decades?
Those assholes.
Chief, is this the right place?
Q?
Sorry.
At least let's change our clothes.
We stink.
And we're starving.
So? :cue
For now, I've notified the staff that the outage was caused
By a mechanical malfunction,
And I've had employees sign non-disclosure agreements to keep them all quiet.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Nothing's been reported in the news yet.
Can I say something?
- I'm a little worried about things. - Oh, really?
I'm worried about how things were handled
Without being reported to headquarters.
For instance, the audit team's investigation of the bus bombing
Seems to be quietly fizzling out.
I honestly don't know how long I can keep covering up around here.
We need to be transparent.
The penalty will be harsh, I'm sure. It's protocol. I know that it will be.
Who takes the penalty?
I do.
Yeah, well, you'd probably take the penalty,
Which is why I'm calling it to your attention.
Just do your job and don't worry about it.
I'll take care of everything.
Right.
I hope you'll give it some thought, even if it's just for ten minutes
While you're in the bathroom.
Dense people have shorter lifespans.
I remember the most interesting thing I learned in the field.
Sometimes people die without ever knowing why.
They always have this look.
"Huh?"
They don't understand at all.
I'm pretty sure that lawyer will have that look.
"Huh?"
Why does that woman always talk like that?
It pisses me off.
Look straight ahead.
It's up to the branch chief if she wants to report to headquarters. :cue
The legal team shouldn't butt their nose where it doesn't belong.
Yeah, it's just that I'm trying to do the job that I was hired to do.
And part of that--
Turn around.
Just do your job properly.
Bus bombing is still being investigated by the audit team.
Don't cross the line.
- Is that understood? - Yeah.
Oh, this is fucking ridiculous.
How does everyone keep getting into my car?
How are you still eating?
These snacks are great.
Did you buy those clothes?
They look stupid.
It's good to have you back, chief.
Are you sure the intel from Babylon is solid?
We're not cops on a stakeout.
How long are we supposed to sit here?
Over there.
Follow my lead.
Capture her alive as quietly as possible.
Copy that.
Light in the face of death :cue
Jeong Jinman?
Remember, alive!
Q?
- When was this? - Two hours, give or take.
- You should have reported it immediately. - My apologies.
It wasn't confirmed information, so I wanted to check with Intel.
If Q finds out it wasn't Jinman that killed her younger brother,
I guarantee that bitch won't just sit there!
Shit! Why is everything so fucking complicated?
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Who's that?
Great. It's the bitch.
What is it?
I haven't heard from you in several days.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG